[{"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 0];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 0];[1, 2];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 1];[1, 2];[2, 0]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 0];[1, 1];[2, 2]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 0];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 1];[1, 2];[2, 0]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 0];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 0];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 1];[1, 0];[2, 2]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 1];[1, 2];[2, 0]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 1];[2, 0]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 2];[1, 0];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 0];[1, 1];[2, 2]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "根据要求连一连", "vaseImg": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "content": [{"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "type": "img"}], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花3.svg", "title": "橙色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "放在"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "最右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的瓶子里。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（3）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花2.svg", "title": "黄色小花"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/小花1.svg", "title": "红色小花"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect2"}], "answers": "{[0, 0];[1, 2];[2, 1]}", "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-07"}]